Ex 02  

Performance tools- 

	Before I began this exercise I had to develop an understand	performance testing so I can perform the tuning. I decided for my ex 01 i would try to profile my CPU Utilization  and Memory  Utilization because it is important for a code to run the most efficient without using too many execution and by not using too much real estate from a memory point of view. 
	I did my profile tooling on a mac, so I tried  using the software Dtrace and Instruments(built in) from Xcode profile tool. After trying to improve the time complexity and utilization I realize instead of having, previous code mode=“r” I decide just write “r”  straight in the open file. This was saving the memory and runtime since I had unnecessary step of declaring. Also for the input file and output file, I initially set the pointer to the files and then I would open the files. However it was smarter and efficient to do that whole process in one step. Overall those were some of small modification I had to make after learning and applying tuning. 